Guide to the Edward E. Shaw Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Edward E. Shaw papers
1967-1976
SC0182
Shaw, Edward E.
8.5 Linear feet (7 boxes)
These records reflect the wide variety of assignments carried out by Shaw as Executive Assistant to William F. Miller. Those files which pre-date Shaw's association with the Provost's office in 1970 were apparently inherited by Shaw and generated by Miller's office during the years 1967 -70. These include, among others, the Provost's Computer Committee and the Stanford Computation Center files. The bulk of Shaw's files fall within the period 1970-73, although they extend to 1976 in some areas. Included are correspondence, reports, minutes, memoranda, proposals, grant files, calendars, patent files, and other materials regarding computation, research funding, budgetary matters, and university administration. All files are of general material and correspondence unless otherwise noted on the folder. The contents have been left in their original arrangement within the folders.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer 1978.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Separated Materials
Mimeographed multiple copies and Stanford catalogs available elsewhere have been removed from the collection. Two maps have been incorporated into the map collection: 1) a map of the Stanford water lines, 1973; 2) map, "Improvement of Parking Lot 'J''', 1973.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Edward E. Shaw, born November 8, 1942, Stanford B.A. in economics 1965, joined the administrative staff of Stanford in the fall of 1965 as a contract administrator in the controller's office. In 1970 he became Assistant to the Vice President for Research, William F. Miller. When Miller was named Vice President and Provost in 1971, Shaw became his Executive Assistant. In 1975 he was named Associate Provost; his later positions included president of the Research Libraries Group, director of the Stanford Center for Information Technology, and associate provost for information systems at Stanford.
Description of the Collection
These records reflect the wide variety of assignments carried out by Shaw as Executive Assistant to William F. Miller. Those files which pre-date Shaw's association with the Provost's office in 1970 were apparently inherited by Shaw and generated by Miller's office during the years 1967 -70. These include, among others, the Provost's Computer Committee and the Stanford Computation Center files. The bulk of Shaw's files fall within the period 1970-73, although they extend to 1976 in some areas. Included are correspondence, reports, minutes, memoranda, proposals, grant files, calendars, patent files, and other materials regarding computation, research funding, budgetary matters, and university administration. All files are of general material and correspondence unless otherwise noted on the folder. The contents have been left in their original arrangement within the folders.
Of special interest are the files on the establishment of BALLOTS (Box 1); the files on affirmative action and salary parity for women (Box 1); Shaw's chronological files (Box 2); and the Wage/Price Freeze files (Box 7). The files in general contain a significant amount of material on research grants, proposals and patents.
Access Terms
BALLOTS Project.; Shaw, Edward E.; Stanford University. Computation Center.; Affirmative action programs --California --Stanford.; Research --Finance.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Papers, 1967-1976; Original Accession
  - Academic Appraisal and Achievement, Comm. on, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic reserve - Reports on (drafts), 1973 Oct-Nov (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic reserve -Master plan/capital budget (draft mss), 1974 Apr 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic reserve - "Master Facilities Plan; 1974-75 Capital Budget; Long-Range Capital Budget Forecast". Preliminary draft, 1974 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic reserve - Status report on physical facility activities, current and planned, (mss), 1976 Mar (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic reserve: (Facilities plan and capital funding forecast, 1976 to 1981). First and second drafts, 1976 Mar (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administrative data processing - three-year plan, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Guide - action file, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Guide - action file, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Guide - action file, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Guide - action file, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Guide - action file, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action - women - salary parity project, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Affirmative Action - women - salary parity project, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Affirmative Action - women - sexism, general material. Folder #1, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action - women - sexism, general material. Folder #2, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action - women - sexism, general material. Folder #3, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Air Force - Contract 1245 and miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Agency for International Development (AID) - 211(d) Grant Program, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - American Indian Project, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Appointment calendar, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Appointment calendar, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Appointment calendar, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Appointment calendar, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - BALLOTS - general material, 1970 Jan-Feb (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - BALLOTS - general material, 1970 Mar-May (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - BALLOTS - general material, 1970 Jun-Aug (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - BALLOTS - general material, 1970 Sep-Dec (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - BALLOTS - general material, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - BALLOTS - Report, Phase II, 1972 Feb (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - BALLOTS - Executive Committee Minutes, 1973 Jan-Aug (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Budgets, Ombudsman (7-RBZ-064), 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cable TV - Sloan Foundation Draft Report, 1974 Apr 30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - list of Fellows, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research, memo re. creation of, 1972 Jun 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files, 1970-1973
    - 1973 Nov (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1973 Oct (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1973 Sep (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1973 Aug (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1973 Jul (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1973 Jun (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1973 May (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1973 Apr (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1973 Mar (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1973 Feb (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1973 Jan (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1972 Dec (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 1972 Nov (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1972 Oct (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1972 Sep (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1972 Aug (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1972 Jul (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1972 Jun (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1972 May (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1972 Apr (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1972 Mar (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1972 Feb (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1972 Jan (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1971 Dec (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 1971 Nov (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1971 Oct (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 1971 Sep (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - 1971 Aug (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 1971 Jul (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 1971 Jun (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 1971 May (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 1971 Apr (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1971 Mar (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 1971 Feb (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 1971 Jan (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 1970 Dec (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 1970 Nov (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 1970 Oct (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 1970 Sep (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - 1970 Aug (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - 1970 Jul (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 1970 Jun (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 1970 May (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 1970 Apr (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 1970 Mar (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 1970 Feb (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 1970 Jan (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Classified research, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Commonwealth Club, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Communications Department, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Conflict of interest, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Conflict of interest - Kuldau-Dann Services, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Cost sharing on research funded by federal funds, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Dept. of Defense - Funding (inquiries), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Dept. of Defense - Research (general), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Dept. of Defense - Research questionnaires sent to schools, and responses, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Dept. of Health, Education & Welfare - general, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Dept. of Health, Education & Welfare - Office of Education, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Facilities planning, construction & utilization - Monthly status reports, 1968-1976
    - 1972 Apr-Oct (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 1973 Dec 1 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 1974 Jan 1-Feb 1 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 1974 Mar 1-Apr 1 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 1974 May 1-Jun 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1974 Jul 1-Aug 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 1974 Sep 1-Oct 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1974 Nov 1-Dec 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 1976 Jun 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Space Bible, 1972 Jan 3 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Faculty, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Faculty - Professorships, endowed chairs, awards, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Freshmen, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Includes report of the freshman Year Project, 1/29/74.
    - Fund raising, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Gift opportunities - active - corresp., 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Gift opportunities - EES, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Gift opportunities being held, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Gifts for research, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Graduate School of Business - Computing, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Graduate School of Business - ESAN, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Graduate School of Business - General, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Graduate School of Business - General, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Housing, Fac/Staff Sub-committee on, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Housing on Campus (all types), 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Institute for Energy Studies, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Institutes within Stanford University, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Labor relations, 1970 Jan-May (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Labor relations, 1970 Jun-Dec (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Labor relations, 1971 Jan-Jun (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Labor relations, 1971 Jul-Dec (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Lyman, Richard: Statement before the Special Subcommittee on Legislation, U.S. Congress, 1974 Jun 4 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Mail summaries, 1974 Jan (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Magnetic Resonance Lab, 1973 Apr-May (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - National Center for Atmospheric Research - Computing Facility Advisory Panel - correspondence, minutes, handbook, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - National Institutes of Health - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - National Institutes of Health - Regulations governing grants - Federal Register, 1970 Jun 4 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - National Science Foundation - Institution grant, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - National Science Foundation - Science Development Program, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - National Science Foundation - Survey, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Overseas studies - miscellaneous material, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Overseas studies - Associate directorship, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Patents, 1969-1976
    - General, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Patent and Licensing Program, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Patent and Licensing Program, 1970 Jan-Mar (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Patent and Licensing Program, 1970 Apr-1971 Jan (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Royalty Sharing Policy, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Software Licensing Policy, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Juvenile Hormone Synthesis, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Personnel - Compensation, charges paid, fourth quarter, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Personnel - Compensation, unemployment - second quarter, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Personnel - Faculty & staff matters, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Personnel - Faculty & staff matters, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Personnel - Salary ranges, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Graphs.
    - Physical Education & Athletics, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Principal investigators, 1969-1971
    - General, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Berke, Dr. Raynold, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Biermann, Alan W., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Dr. J. Martin, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - DeVoto, R.S. and Koutosoyannis, S.P., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Duffield, Dr. Allen, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Eaton, Dr. Monroe D., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Forrest, Irene, 1970 (?) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Goldstein, Dora, M. D., 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Kohen-Raz, Reuven, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Loew, Dr. Gilda, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - McAlister, John, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - McIntosh, S.C., Jr., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Moller, Cleve, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Dr. Marion E., 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Tachibana, Dr. Shunro, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Tyler, Dr. G.L., 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Proposals, 1969-1974
    - Academic Research and its Relationship to Society, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Child Care Center, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Cohen, B., and Closed Circuit TV., Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Community Scholars Program, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Computation Center, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Computer Science Dept., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Division of Student Special Services, U.S. Office of Education, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Engineering-Design Division, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Environmental Proposal, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Expanded Academic Planning Office - draft proposal to Ford Foundation, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - GSB Proposal to Sloan Foundation - Urban Management Program, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Herrmann Proposal on Mechanics of Cortical Bone, 1970 Feb (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Knight Foundation (Lyle Nelson) - Journalism Proposal, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Meindl, James D., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Models of Group Decision Processes in an International Context - Ford Foundation Proposal, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - NASA-ASEE Engineering Systems Design Summer Fac. Fellowship Program, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - NASA. Folder #1, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - NASA. Folder #2, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - National Institutes of Mental Health, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Proposals awarded, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Santa Clara Co. Planning Dept., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Stanford International Science and Technology Education Center, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Undergraduate Program on the Theme of Socialization - School of Education, 1971 Jun 7 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Undergraduate Program on Values, Technology and Society, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Provost's Computer Committee, 1968-1975
    - #2980 - Provost's Computer Committee, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - #2981 - General, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - #2982 - Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - #2983 - Membership, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - #2984 - Budgets, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - #2985 - Finance Subcommittee, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - #2986 - Research Subcommittee, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - #2987 - Teaching Requirements Subcommittee, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Provost' s Staff for Development. Green Folder Group, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      Includes Minutes.
    - Provost's Staff for Development. Green Folder Group, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Publications, miscell. Stanford - general material, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Report: "A Behavioral Approach to the Study of Pollution & Other Externalities", by J. Dana and F. Rubenstein, 1970 Jun 10 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Research Administration - Human subjects, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Research Administration - General, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Research Administration - Information retrieval system, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Research Advisory Group, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Research assistants, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Research, Committee on, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Research Funding, Committee on - Aeor & Astro, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Research Funding, Committee on - Computer Science, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Research Development Fund, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Research Development Fund - Proposals submitted, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Research grants & contracts, Non-government, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Research - Miscellaneous material re., 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Research organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Research titles, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - ROTC at Stanford, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Sabbaticals, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Schools, depts., institutes, general, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Sponsored projects - general, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Sponsored projects - Research administration monthly summaries, 1972 Aug-1973 Jul (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Sponsored projects - Research administration monthly summaries, 1973 Aug-1974 May (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Sponsored projects - Research administration monthly summaries, 1974 Jun-Dec (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Band, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Computation Center, 1967-1975
    - Comp. Facility Advisory Panel meeting, Boulder, Colo., 1970 Mar 23 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Dickens, Charles - Computation Head, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Financial review, 1970 Oct 30 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - IBM correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - IBM correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - IBM disclosure, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - IBM general, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - International Computer Forum, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Long Range Computer Planning Study. Folder # 1, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Long Range Computer Planning Study. Folder #2, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Long Range Computer Planning Study. Folder #3, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Long Range Computer Planning Study. Folder #4, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Phillips, T.D., 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Project INFO, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Proposal: "A Parallel Computing Network at Stanford". Folder #1, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Proposal: "A Parallel Computing Network at Stanford". Folder #2, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Sigma 5 depreciation, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Stanford Computer Forum, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Usage File, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Stanford University Hospital - Physicians Assistants Program, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Student-initiated projects, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Student-initiated projects, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Student Project Initiated Fund (SPIF), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Students - General material, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - SWOPSI - Task force on education at Stanford, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Terman Engineering Center - Architectural program index, Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Training Grant policy, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Undergraduate Research Opportunities (UROP), 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - University Budget Priorities Advisory Commission, 1972-1976
    - Meetings, 1975 Sep 22-Nov 7 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, 1975 Nov 14-1976 Jan 8 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Meetings, 1976 Jan 16-Jun 17 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Corresp., meetings, 1976 Jun-Dec (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Sub-Committee on Computing. Folder #1, 1976 Jan-May (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Sub-Committee on Computing. Folder #2, 1976 Jan-May (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - University memos. Folder #1, 1973 Nov-1974 May (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - University memos. Folder #2, 1973 Nov-1974 May (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Vice President & Provost, Office of - office matters, miscell., 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Includes Wm. F. Miller "Fact Sheet", undated.
    - Vice Presidents Group, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Vice Presidents Group - Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Wage/price freeze, 1967-1972
    - External policies, guidelines, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Faculty and staff salaries - schools, depts., 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Implementation guidelines, 1971 Sep 4 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Individual inquiries, miscell., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Internal - Guidelines, status reports, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Report, Princeton University, 1971 Jan 20 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Student salaries and stipends, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Wheel Chair Students - Miscell. material, also re. CHAIR (Committee on Handicapped, Assistance, Information and Research), 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Xerox Corporation, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)